Michael Alpert collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 9: Miscellaneous recordings, performances, lectures, and interviews
  - Unlabeled recording with interviews in Yiddish, undated, AFC 2017/048: SR0590; Alpert 1087; 1 minidisc
  - Unlabeled recording with interviews in Yiddish, undated, AFC 2017/048: SR0613; Alpert 1126; 1 sound cassette
  - Unlabeled recording with interviews in Yiddish, February 2004, AFC 2017/048: SR0642; Alpert 1175-1176; 1 sound cassette
  - Unlabeled recording with interviews in English, undated, AFC 2017/048: SR0574; Alpert 1073; 1 minidisc
  - Unlabeled recording with interviews in English, undated, AFC 2017/048: SR0622; Alpert 1144-1145; 1 sound cassette
  - Unlabeled recording with Klezmer music performances, undated, AFC 2017/048: SR0560; Alpert 1057; 1 minidisc
  - Unlabeled recording with Klezmer music performances, undated, AFC 2017/048: SR0567; Alpert 1066; 1 minidisc
  - Unlabeled recording with Klezmer music performances, undated, AFC 2017/048: SR0573; Alpert 1072; 1 minidisc
  - Unlabeled recording with Klezmer music performances, undated, AFC 207/048: SR0580; Alpert 1079; 1 minidisc
  - Unlabeled recording with Klezmer music performances, May 3, 2002, AFC 2017/048: SR0587; Alpert 1084; 1 minidisc
  - Unlabeled recording with Klezmer music performances, undated, AFC 2017/048: SR0589; Alpert 1086; 1 minidisc
  - Unlabeled recording with Klezmer music performances, undated, AFC 2017/048: SR0592; Alpert 1089; 1 minidisc
  - Unlabeled recording with Klezmer music performances, undated, AFC 2017/048: SR0593; Alpert 1090; 1 minidisc
  - Unlabeled recording with Klezmer music performances, undated, AFC 2017/048: SR0594; Alpert 1091; 1 minidisc
  - Unlabeled recording with songs in Yiddish, undated, AFC 2017/048: SR0466; Alpert 882-883; 1 minidisc
  - Unlabeled recording with songs in Yiddish, undated, AFC 2017/048: SR0522; Alpert 997; 1 minidisc
  - Unlabeled recording with songs in Yiddish, undated, AFC 2017/048: SR0555; Alpert 1052; 1 minidisc
  - Unlabeled recording with songs in Yiddish, undated, AFC 2017/048: SR0562; Alpert 1059; 1 minidisc
  - Unlabeled recording with songs in Yiddish, undated, AFC 2017/048: SR0563; Alpert 1060; 1 minidisc
  - Unlabeled recording with songs in Yiddish, undated, AFC 2017/048: SR0571; Alpert 1070; 1 minidisc
  - Unlabeled recording with songs in Yiddish, undated, AFC 2017/048: SR0572; Alpert 1071; 1 minidisc
  - Unlabeled recording with songs in Yiddish, undated, AFC 2017/048: SR0576; Alpert 1075; 1 minidisc
  - Unlabeled recording with songs in Yiddish, undated, AFC 2017/048: SR0577; Alpert 1076; 1 sound cassette
  - Unlabeled recording with songs in Yiddish, undated, AFC 2017/048: SR0585; Alpert 1082; 1 sound cassette
  - Digital surrogates of recordings in Series 9, 1979-2004, afc2017048_dc001; Digital copies of audio are available as both WAV and MP3 files. PDF files depicting the outside of each audio carrier are also available for many of the recordings.; 107 WAV, 107 MP3, 26 PDF
Related Publications
Alpert, Michael. 'All My Life a Musician': Ben Bazyler, a European Klezmer in America. In American Klezmer: Its Roots and Offshoots, edited by Mark Slobin, 73-83. Berkeley: University of California Press, 2002.
Beregovski, Moshe. Jewish Instrumental Folk Music: The Collections and Writings of Moshe Beregovski. Edited and translated by Mark Slobin, Robert A. Rothstein, and Michael Alpert. Syracuse, NY: Syracuse University Press, 2001.